Sengoku
Let's get to sleep.
I kicked your table! Sorry!
Hey, it's late. Keep your voice down!
I'll put my stuff over here.
Does Kakeru have friends close
enough to invite for a sleepover?
I'm sure he does.
Sengoku-san, I want the loft bed!
Sure. I'll tidy it up for you.
No need! I'll take it as-is!
It's really messy.
Really, it's fine!
I'm serious. There are more books
than can be considered safe.
It's like it was falling rock zone.
I-I...
I love falling rock zones!
What are you talking about?!
Well, if you're sure, I guess I don't mind.
Okay, is that settled?
I can take the floor.
The floor?
Well, I can take the floor...
Snore
except someone's already sleeping there.
That was fast, Miyamura-kun!
Miyamura, move over.
S-Sorry it's so cramped.
Nah, it's fine.
It's so hot...
Ahhh
No, idiot! Don't take that off!
You'll be throwing away all your hard work!
What's the matter?
It's nothing!
Good night!
Good night.
I'll get to sleep, too.
Cramped
There's no space for me to sleep.
If Ishikawa-kun goes here...
and Miyamura-kun goes here...
Simulation
Ishikawa—
He's asleep!
Sleepover
M-Miyamura-kun?
Hey...
No, Hori-san...
Those are my organs.
Chill
What kind of dream are you having?
Motoko, wait, is that...?
Oh, it's just a goldfish.
Thump
A goldfish? And who is Motoko?
Silence
Now what?
I wish I cleaned my room more regularly.
Keep your room clean, idiot.
Mom, I'm sorry.
No, wait! It's not messy!
My room's just small!
Just look at all these books!
My dad has books in here, too!
Animals of the World Insects Fish The Human Body
Those all take up space.
That's why there's no place to sleep.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, Iura-kun...
Why are you up?
I need to use the restroom.
Sengoku-san, aren't you going to sleep?
Why didn't you say something?
We're the ones imposing.
It just didn't seem right to wake anyone up.
Wake up and fall in!
You don't need to do that!
What?
Sengoku doesn't have space to sleep?
You should've said so, idiot.
Sorry.
I'll move closer to the wall,
that lump who isn't waking up
gets moved to the bookcase...
Sengoku, can you cut yourself in half?
No.
Maybe if you and Miyamura
slept in the loft...
I don't mind.
How? There's only enough room for one.
You'll both fit.
It's one half plus one half.
They add up to one.
Damn, I didn't want to,
but there's no other choice.
Miyamura-kun, let's go up to the loft.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'll go home, Kyosuke-san...
Hey!
The two of us managed to squeeze in,
but I don't like this.
No, idiot! Don't take that off!
The pool... Damn...
Oh, I'll go change over there.
I accidentally sprayed Miyamura
with a hose the other day.
But he refused to take off his uniform.
I wonder why.
Sengoku-san, sorry!
I left my cell phone...
Sorry, I just remembered...
I broke it in half, mangled it, turned it
into dust, and washed it down the gutter.
Wait, wait, wait, wait! Just hold on!
No, don't mind me.
No matter what you do,
you'll still be Sengoku-san.
That makes it sound worse!
It's not what it looks like!
Stop and listen to me!
No, I've seen all I needed to see.
You can't convince me otherwise.
Don't be stubborn about it!
I respect you, Sengoku-san.
So I want to hear you out.
It's just... There's...
Don't trail off! You've got it wrong!
I just tried to take his shirt off!
I have a reason! I'm serious!
It's nothing more than—
You were trying to take his shirt off...
I respect you.
He means it in a different way
Oh, no!
No, Iura-kun!
Listen to me!
Iura-kun, say something!
Don't go back down in silence!
Miyamura's under suspicion.
Sengoku's pretty clever.
Hey, Sengoku, why don't you sleep down here?
I'm up here because there's not enough room!
Well...
We just need to move the table.
We'll take the books off and stand it up.
How did I not think of that?
What did we spend all that time doing?
Yeah, seriously.
What happened?!
It's so early—
Sting
Shu was laughing in his sleep,
and it freaked me out.
I just laughed in my sleep
and got hit for it.
Definitely not the most
pleasant ways to wake up.
Anyway, good morning.
Morning.
Good morning.
I don't think I got much sleep.
Miyamura?
Miyamura!
He's still asleep.
He just sleeps and sleeps.
If he doesn't have school,
he'll sleep until evening.
That's too much sleep.
I-I'll wake him up.
Why are you looking at me like that?!
I'm just waking him up! Nothing else!
Me, too! Me, too!
I'll wake him up, too!
It doesn't take that many people, idiot!
I'm going up first!
Hey, Shu, wait!
Don't! I'll go!
Hey, it's my futon!
Iura-kun, get off!
On
Miyamura
Aw, do I have to?
Um, good morning.
Good morning.
Shake
Morning.
Is it morning?
Yup.
Why are you all up here?
How can you ask that?
Don't you realize the danger you're in?
Danger?!
Hey, Iura-kun, let's swap positions.
We have to be careful
or Miyamura will be crushed.
Shu, stay right where you are.
Sengoku might do something
funny to Miyamura!
No, I won't!
Don't look at me like that! Turn around!
I t-t-trust you, C-Class President.
Liar! You're stuttering like crazy!
But what are you doing
so early in the morning?
This is your wake-up call.
This isn't a call.
I need to use the restroom.
Ishikawa, go down.
Back it up.
No, idiot! What if Sengoku
finds an opening to Miyamura?
I don't care! I really
need to use the restroom!
Fine, but I tried.
I hope you can hold it.
I'm eighteen, so I think I can.
So, Sengoku-san, why are you after Miyamura?
That's a rude way to put it!
Listen, this is part of my job
as a class representative!
A class rep is supposed to
undress another boy?
Please, just tell me why
Miyamura-kun hides his skin.
Whimper
Uh...
I don't understand.
About Miyamura...
The truth is...
It was a long trip to
the class president's restroom.
Huh? What?
What's up?
Miyamura.
I covered for you.
Huh?
A bazooka in his solar plexus...
Whisper
A bazooka shoots out of his solar plexus...
Just what did you cover?
They're talking about a bazooka.
You know, that thing you have.
More
misunderstandings
He wouldn't take off his
uniform when Remi sprayed him.
What? Is this about Miyamura?
Who else?
How would I know when
you just blurt that out?
I see. Miyamura...
Ishikawa-kun, do you know something?
Nope, not a thing!
Man, it's cold.
Let me warm up in here, Class President.
Oh.
Ishikawa-kun is here, too.
Hey.
It's a Miyamura flying into the flame.
Huh? There's no fire here.
So you've come!
Why are you so happy to see me?
Miyamura-kun...
Are you feeling hot?
No, I came in here because I'm cold.
But you'll start feeling
hot if you stay here.
See how Ishikawa-kun took off his blazer?
H-He's being so obvious!
Really?
I'm still feeling cold, so I'll keep it on.
Damn!
Miyamura, you don't wear
a school sweater, right?
No, I don't own one.
You should try one.
Glare
It'll look great on you.
I know. I'll trade you mine.
Class President, you're scaring me.
Here.
Wow, a school sweater!
He's going to change into it!
At last I'll learn what
Miyamura-kun's been hiding!
Miyamura said his tattoos
show through a white shirt.
He'll definitely see
through Sengoku's trick—
You have got to be kidding me.
Now, take off your sweater, Miyamura-kun!
He's gonna find out, Miyamura!
Ow...
Are you okay?
No!
This is so warm!
Class President, this material is so nice!
What do you think? How does it look?
Saved
the day
It looks great!
I thought that would work.
What would?
Okay, I'll ask you straight-up.
Why don't you like to take off your clothes?
Because I'm a rational person.
Finally caught on
I'm not telling you to walk around naked!
I mean when you change
for phys ed and stuff.
What? What do you mean, Class President?
Are you obsessed with me?
No! I just really want to know!
Why, though?
What do you mean, "Why"?
Because it's clearly not normal.
Why, though?
Calm down, Miyamura-kun!
The class president is bullying me!
Give back my sweater!
Miyamura-kun!
When did you get a school sweater?
Why were you running so fast?
Kakeru.
I don't remember that sweater.
He got away.
Wow, it's so cold!
Remi, sorry you had to wait.
Pat
Let's head home.
Sure.
It's cold.
It snowed, too.
We'll have to wait a while for spring.
It sucks that you have to wear
a skirt with your legs exposed.
So cold...
Hand. Hand.
Here.
It's cold.
Huh?
Remi-san—
I'm warm now.
But I'm cold.
I'm warm, though.
Warm!
I see.
Hand.
Yeah, okay.
Silence
Hold my hand!
She's angry at me.
Make sure to walk properly.
It feels warm.
Sengoku-kun, are you warm?
Yeah.
Your hand is so thin and bony
that mine isn't so warm.
Oh.
That must be awkward.
No, I'm sorry my hand is so small.
It's fine.
Want to go somewhere?
Nope.
We're walking a little fast.
I walk fast if I don't pay attention.
Then pay attention.
Right.
Walk a little slower.
We'll stop, though.
Oh, you really stopped.
Aren't you going home?
Your place is right over there.
You're cold, right?
Hug...
Never mind.
Hug.
Remi.
Remi-san, let me move my arms a second.
Thanks.
Kiss.
Hey, we're on the street.
Push
Understood.
Good.
No kissing
on the street
Library
Mathematics II
Remi, are you ready to go?
The library's about to close.
Oh, you're right!
I think I overworked my brain.
You're working hard.
Do you need any help with math today?
Nope, I can do it myself.
Yeah?
Yep!
Let's go, Sakura.
Sengoku-kun.
Can we walk home together?
Sure.
Are you ready?
Yeah, sure.
Is it that cold out?
Are you with a cold girl or something?
I didn't say that.
Hori, is something up?
Huh? Where's Remi-chan?
I'm not sure.
Those two don't usually
go home by themselves.
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
No, it's totally normal.
I don't spend every minute
of the day with Miyamura, either.
Yeah, you're right!
Kyon-kyon, Yuki-chan!
Have you seen Sengoku-kun or Sakura?
I went to the restroom,
but now I can't find them.
Where could they be?
Do you feel cold?
No, not at all.
Suspicion Filter ON
Oh, I just saw—
What was that for? It hurt!
Don't say it!
Why not? It's fine, right?
Just don't!
It's not like that, right?
What?
Are you hiding something?
Huh? O-O-Of course not.
Hori...
Maybe they're in the student council room.
I'll try calling.
Huh? What?
L-Look! On the window over there!
There's an, um, giant bug!
A bug? Where?
Look, right there!
I don't think this is really
Hori's problem, though.
Return
trays here
Welcome!
Have you decided on your order?
Should we sit here?
Sure.
What's up, Ishikawa?
I just saw Sengoku.
He's with Kono-san.
Oh.
The thing is, Ayasaki isn't with them.
And Kono-san was holding
what looked like a present.
You're spilling your drink! It's everywhere!
Is Sengoku-san cheating on her?!
We can't be sure!
Does that mean Ayasaki-san is free now?
This is my chance!
We really can't be sure of that!
And why do I have to wipe this up?
You should be doing this!
I figured that loud voice
belonged to Iura-kun.
I'm not thinking of anything underhanded!
You're not with Ayasaki today, huh?
Not today.
I'm not sure how to interpret that response.
Don't tell Remi that you saw me.
What'll happen if I do tell her?
Suddenly
bold
Shu, shut up.
Don't tell Remi.
I'm very sorry. I will take it to my grave.
What was that about?
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Aw, on the next mock exam? I can't!
I've never scored above a forty in math.
Go for sixty.
I can't.
Well, if you score at least sixty,
we'll go to that chocolate shop you like...
and get...
Premium cookies?!
Yeah, that.
W-Well, I'm not motivated by material things.
Anyway, good luck!
Next is...
Mathematics Practice Test Answer Sheet
That's great.
You've never gotten higher
than forty before, right?
She says she's not motivated
by material things.
Huh?
Good morning, Remi.
Oh, Sakura!
You left without me yesterday!
I didn't know what to think!
I'm sorry.
You see, Remi...
This is for you.
Cookies?!
B-But why?!
I didn't get a sixty on the mock exam...
What do you mean?
I was just in the area and picked these up.
Wow, you were right. These are delicious.
I-I want one, too.
Go ahead.
I make cookies myself from time to time,
but ones from a shop
can really hit the spot.
Sakura, thank you.
Did you say something?
Nope!
Oh?
Shouldn't Sengoku-kun have some, too?
Here's what he said:
"No. If I had any, there
would be less for Remi."
That was exactly like him, Sakura!
I know, right?
You're really good at impressions!
That was nothing like me! Damn you, Sakura!
I thought you wanted to stay hidden.
Sakura!
There, there, there, there...
Next time
page.7 Friends